Little girl?
I'm a policeman.
Little girl.
Don't be afraid, okay?
Oh my God.
-What's the difference
between men and women?
- This a joke?
- No, I'm serious.
I never met a woman
who knew how to turn off alight.
They're born thinking
the switch only goes one way--
- on.
They're struck blind
the second they leave a room.
I mean every woman
I ever let have a key--
I swear to God,
it's like I come home,
house all lit up.
And my job,
you see, apparently--
because my chromosomes
happen to be different--
is I've then gotta walk
through that house,
turn off every single light
this chick left on.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, baby. Mmm.
Oh, Reverend Shane is
preaching to you now, boy.
Then-- the same chick, mind you--
she'll bitch about global warming.
You see, this is- this is
when Reverend Shane wants
to quote from
the guy gospel and say,
"Darling, maybe you and every other
pair of boobs on this planet
just figure out the light switch,
you see, goes both ways,
maybe we wouldn't have so much
global warming." You know?
- You say that?
- Mmm.
Yeah, well, a polite version.
Still, man, that earns me this look
of loathing you would not believe.
And that's when
the "Exorcist" voice pops out.
"You sound just like my damn father!
Always yelling
about the power bill,
telling me to tum off
the damn lights!"
- And what do you say to that?
- I know what I want to say.
I want to say,
"Bitch, you mean to tell me
you've been hearing this
your entire life
and you are still too damn stupid
to learn how to turn off a switch?"
You know, I--
I don't actually say that though.
- That would be bad.
- Right right.
Yeah, I go with the--
I go with the polite version there too.
- Very wise.
- Yes sir.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well.
So how's it with Lori, man?
She's good- she's good
at turning off lights.
Really good. I'm the one
who sometimes forgets.
Not what I meant.
- We didn't have a great night.
- Hey look, man,
I may have failed
to amuse with my sermon,
but I did try.
The least you can
do is-- is speak.
That's-- that's what
she always says.
"Speak. Speak."
You'd think I was the most
closed-mouth son of a bitch ever
to hear her tell it.
Do you express your thoughts?
Do you share your feelings,
that kind of stuff?
The thing is--
lately, whenever I try,
everything I say
makes her impatient,
like she didn't want
to hear it after all.
It's like she's...
Pissed at me all the time
and I don't know why.
Look, man. That's just shit
couples go through.
Yeah, it's a phase.
The last thing
she said this morning,
"Sometimes I wonder
if you even care about us at all."
She said that
in front of our kid.
Imagine going to school
with that in your head.
The difference
between men and women?
I would never say something
that cruel to her...
And certainly not
in front of Carl.
All available units,
high-speed pursuit in progress.
Linden County units
request local assistance.
Highway 18 eastbound. GTA, ADW,
2-17, 2-4-3.
Advise extreme caution.
Suspects are two male Caucasians.
Be advised they have fired
upon police officers.
One Linden County officer
is wounded.
Unit 1, unit 3, to eastbound Route 18,
two miles west of Interstate 85.
Will patch in
Linden County sheriff radio.
Roger that. We're five minutes south
of the Route 18 intersection.
Dispatch, unit 1 and unit 3,
we are 10-97 and code 100,
Highway 18,
E.B. of interstate, please advise.
10-9,
we just got word from Linden County
that they're off 18,
now southbound--
Old French Road
is closed down there
so they're gonna head
back onto 18.
Sounds like they chasing those idiots
up and down every back road we've got.
Maybe we'll get on one of them
video shows, you know?
Like "World's Craziest Police Chases."
What do you think?
What I think, Leon,
is you need to stay focused,
make sure you've got a round
in the chamber and your safety off.
Would be kinda cool,
getting on one of them shows.
Holy shit.
- Gun gun gun!
- Put it down!
Put the gun down!
Ah!
Rick!
I'm all right!
I saw you get tagged, man.
That scared the hell out of me.
Me too.
That son of a bitch shot me.
- You believe that?
- What? It catch you in your vest?
Yeah.
Shane, you do not tell Lori
that happened-- ever.
You understand? Ah!
- Police, move in!
- No no no no no no no.
- You see where he come from?
- Shh shh shh shh.
No no no no
no no no no.
He's hit!
Leon! You get
that ambulance down here!
You tell them there's
an officer down! You do it now!
Okay, shh shh shh shh.
I'm here. Hey, you look at me.
You stay with me.
You hear me?
Shh shh shh. Okay.
I'm right here, Rick.
Stay with me. You hear me?
Shh shh. That's it. Do you hear me?
Shh shh shh. Okay.
I'm right here with you.
Stay with me.
- Shh shh. That's it. I'm right here.
Dispatch, we have an officer down.
Request paramedics,
please respond.
Route 18 two miles west of I-85.
Repeat, officer down.
Request immediate response.
Hey, bud.
We're still here.
We're still hanging in.
I'm sorry, man.
I know I say the same crap
every time I come in here.
Everybody pitched in on these.
They-- they wanted me
to bring 'em down.
They send their love,
and they just--
they hope you come back real soon.
Linda and Diane from dispatch,
they picked these out.
Probably could tell, huh?
I'm just gonna set these
on your side table, okay?
That vase-
that's something special.
'Fess up. You steal that for me
at Grandma Jean's house?
I hope you left her
that spoon collection.
Shane?
Shane, you in the john?
Nurse, help.
Ah!
Ah.
Ah. Ah. Oh shit.
Lori.
Lori!
Carl. Carl!
Shoot
Lori! Carl!
Lori! Carl.
Is this real?
Am I here?
Wake-- wake up.
- Daddy! Daddy!
- Carl.
Carl. I found you.
Daddy, I got the sumbitch!
I'm gonna smack him dead!
He say something?
I thought I heard him say something.
- He called me Carl.
- Son, you know they don't talk.
Hey, mister,
what's that bandage for?
W-- what?
What kind of wound?
You answer me, damn you.
What's your wound?
You tell me...
Or I will kill you.
You got
that bandage changed now.
It was pretty rank.
What was the wound?
- Gunshot.
- Gunshot?
What else? Anything?
Gunshot ain't enough?
Look, I ask and you answer.
That's common courtesy, right?
Did you get bit?
- Bit?
- Bit, chewed,
maybe scratched--
anything like that?
No, I got shot.
Just shot as far as I know.
Hey. Just let me.
Feels cool enough.
Fever would've killed you by now.
I don't think I have one.
Be hard to miss.
Take a moment,
look how sharp it is.
You try anything,
I will kill you with it.
And don't you think I won't.
Come on out when you're able.
Come on.
This place--
Fred and Cindy Drake's?
Never met 'em.
I've been here.
This is their place.
It was empty when we got here.
Don't do that.
They'll see the light.
There's more of them
out there than usual.
I never should've fired
that gun today.
Sound draws them.
Now they're all over the street.
Stupid-- using a gun.
But it all happened so fast,
I didn't think.
You shot that man today.
- Man?
- It weren't no man.
What the hell was that
out of your mouth just now?
It wasn't a man.
You shot him in the street
out front- a man.
Friend, you need glasses.
It was a walker.
Come on. Sit down
before you fall down.
Here.
Daddy,
blessing.
Yeah.
Lord, we thank Thee for this food,
Thy blessings.
And we ask You to watch over us
in these crazy days.
-Amen.
- Amen.
Hey, mister, you even know
what's going on?
I woke up today in the hospital,
came home
and that's all I know.
But you know about
the dead people, right?
Yeah, I saw a lot of that--
out on the loading dock,
piled in trucks.
No, not the ones they put down.
The ones they didn't--
the walkers,
like the one I shot today.
'Cause he'd have ripped into you,
tried to eat you,
taken some flesh at least.
Well, I guess if this is
the first you're hearing it,
I know how it must sound.
They're out there now?
In the street?
Yeah.
They get more active
after dark sometimes.
Maybe it's the cool air or--
hell, maybe it's just
me firing that gun today.
But we'll be fine
as long as we stay quiet.
Probably wander off by morning.
But listen,
one thing I do know--
don't you get bit.
I saw your bandage
and that's what we were afraid of.
Bites kill you.
The fever burns you out.
But then after a while...
You come back.
Seen it happen.
Come on.
Carl-- he your son?
Well, you--
you said his name today.
He's a little younger
than your boy.
And he's with his mother?
I hope so.
Dad.
Hey.
Did you ask him?
Your gunshot--
we've got a little bet going.
My boy says
you're a bank robber.
Yeah, that's me,
the deadliest Dillinger. Kapow.
-- Sheriff's deputy.
Uh-huh.
Hey, it's okay. Daddy's here.
It's nothing.
One of them must've
bumped a car.
- Are you sure?
- It happened once before.
It went on for a few minutes.
Get the light, Duane.
it's the blue one on the street,
the same one as last time.
I think we're okay.
That noise--
won't it bring more of them?
Nothing we can do about it now.
Just have to
wait 'em out till morning.
She's here.
Don't look.
Get away from the windows.
I said go. Go on.
- Duane. Duane, quiet now.
Come on. Quiet now.
Shh shh.
It's okay. Here.
Cry into the pillow.
Do you remember?
Shh. Shh.
She, um--
she died in that other room
on that bed in there.
There was nothing I--
I could do about it.
That fever, man,
her skin gave off
a heat like a furnace.
I should've--
I should've put her down, man.
I should've put her down.
I know that, but I--
you know what?
I just didn't have it in me.
She's the mother of my child.
Are we sure they're dead?
I have to ask
at least one more time.
They dead,
except for something in the brain.
That's why
it's got to be the head.
Y'all all right?
I need a moment.
They're alive--
my wife and son.
At least they were
when they left.
How can you know?
By the look of this place--
I found empty drawers
in the bedroom.
They packed some clothes-- not a lot,
but enough to travel.
You know anybody could've broken in
here and stole them clothes, right?
You see the framed photos
on the walls?
Neither do I.
Some random thief take
those too, you think?
Our photo albums,
family pictures" all gone.
Photo albums.
My wife-- same thing.
There I am
packing survival gear,
she's grabbing photo alb...
They're in Atlanta, I bet.
That's right.
- Why there?
- Refugee center.
A huge one they said,
before the broadcast stopped.
Military protection, food, shelter.
They told people to go there,
said it'd be safest.
Plus they got that disease place.
The Center
for Disease Control
said they were working out
how to solve this thing.
Gas lines have been down
for maybe a month.
The station's got
its own propane system.
Pilot's still on.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Oh my Lord.
- Hot water!
- Ah!
That feels good, right?
-- Bring it around, bring it
Bring it, bring it,
bring it around, uh!
Yeah. I'm wet.
Take that. What?
Whoo!
Duane.
Dressing room back there.
What do you say, Duane?
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Atlanta sounds like a good deal.
Safer anyway-- people.
That's where we were headed.
Things got crazy.
Man, you wouldn't
believe the panic.
Streets weren't Ht to be on.
And then my--
my wife couldn't travel--
no, not with her hurt--
so we had to find a place to lay low.
And then after she died,
we just stayed hunkered down.
I guess we just froze in place.
Plan to move on?
Haven't worked up to it yet.
A lot of it's gone missing.
Daddy, can I learn
to shoot?
- I'm old enough.
- Hell yes, you're gonna learn,
but we've got to do it carefully,
teach you to respect the weapon.
That's right. it's not a toy.
You pull the trigger,
you have to mean it.
Always remember that, Duane.
Yes sir.
Here. Load up.
You take that one.
Nothing fancy.
The scope's accurate.
Conserve your ammo.
It goes faster than you think,
especially at target practice.
- Duane.
- Uh-huh?
- Take this to the car.
- Okay.
Are you sure
you won't come along?
A few more days.
By then Duane will know how to shoot
and I won't be so rusty.
You've got one battery.
I'll turn mine on a few minutes
every day at dawn.
You get up there,
that's how you'll find me.
- You think ahead.
- Can't afford not to,
- not anymore.
- Listen, one thing--
they may not seem
like much one at a time,
but in a group,
all riled up and hungry--
- man, you watch your ass.
- You too.
You're a good man, Rick.
I hope you find your wife and son.
Be seeing you, Duane.
- Take care of your old man.
- Yes sir.
Leon Basset?
I didn't think much of him--
careless and dumb-- but...
I can't leave him like this.
You know they'll hear the shot.
Let's not be here
when they show up.
Let's go, son. Come on.
Read your comic books awhile.
Daddy'll be upstairs.
- Daddy?
- it's all right, Duane!
You stay there, son.
Don't you come up here.
Jenny.
Come on, baby.
I'm sorry this happened to you.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Yeah.
-- Broadcasting on emergency channel.
Will be approaching
Atlanta on Highway 85.
Anybody reads, please respond.
Hello. Hello.
Can anybody hear my voice?
Anybody out there?
Anybody hears me,
please respond.
Hello, can you hear my voice?
Hello. Hello.
Can anybody hear my voice?
- Hey. Hello?
- Can you hear my voice?
Yes, I can hear you.
You're coming through. Over.
If anybody reads,
please respond.
Broadcasting
on emergency channel.
Will be approaching
Atlanta on Highway 85.
If anybody reads, please respond.
We're just outside the city.
- Damn it.
Hello? Hello?
He couldn't hear me.
- I couldn't warn him.
- Try to raise him again.
Come on, son, you know best
how to work this thing.
Hello, hello. ls the person
who called still on the air?
This is Officer Shane Walsh
broadcasting to person unknown.
Please respond.
He's gone.
There are others.
it's not just us.
We knew there would be, right?
That's why we left the CB on.
A lot of good it's been doing.
- Okay.
- And I've been saying for a week
we ought to put signs up on 85
and warn people away from the city.
Folks got no idea
what they're getting into.
Well, we haven't had time.
I think we need to make time.
Yeah, that--
that's a luxury we can't afford.
We are surviving here.
We are day to day.
And who the hell would
you propose we send?
I'll go. Give me a vehicle.
Nobody goes anywhere alone.
You know that.
Yes sir.
Hey hey hey.
Go on, take a seat, bud.
You're all right.
Go on. You're all right.
What, are you pissed at me?
You can be pissed at me all you want.
it's not gonna change anything.
I'm not putting you
in danger, okay?
I'm not doing it for anything.
That make you feel like
sometimes you want
to slap me upside the head--
tell you what, girl:
you feel that need, you go right ahead.
I'm right here. Go on.
You cannot walk off like that,
all half-cocked.
Look, you do not want to do it
for my sake or your sake, that's fine.
But just-- you do it for him.
That boy has been
through too much
and he's not losing
his mother too, okay?
Okay?
I'm a good mom.
You tell me "okay."
Hmm?
it's not hard.
All right? Hey.
Mom?
What's up, bud?
She's in there. Go on.
Hey, I don't want you to worry.
Your mama's not
going anywhere, okay?
Yeah? Yeah?
- Go finish your chores. Okay.
- Okay.
Hello?
Police officer out here.
Can I borrow some gas?
Hello?
Anybody home?
- Easy now. Easy.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Nothing like that.
More like a proposal.
Atlanta's just down
the road a ways.
It's safe there--
food, shelter, people.
Other horses too, I bet.
How's that sound?
There we go. Good boy.
Good boy. Good boy.
Now come with me. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Good boy.
Just go easy, okay?
I haven't done this for years.
- Whoa. Whoa whoa whoa!
Easy now.
Easy, boy.
Easy. Easy.
Easy. Easy. Eas--
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Whoa whoa whoa.
Let's go.
- Whoa.
- Steady.
There's just a few.
Nothing we can't outrun.
Okay. Whoa whoa whoa.
Whoa.
- Hyah!
Oh shit.
Oh God.
Oh God. Oh God.
Shoot
Lori, Carl, I'm sorry.
Oh... God.
Ah.
Oh God.
Hey, you.
Dumbass.
Yeah, you in the tank.
Are you cozy in there?
- I Yeah I
Drifting on the spaceway
By the Betelgeuse Hotel
Mapping out constellations
Of the place I know so well
Sifting through the system
For the piece
that knows my name
Endlessly I listen
In the master game
Welcome to my world
Welcome
to my world
Welcome to my only world
Welcome to
my only world
It is full of space junk
But your words
are coming through
I'm riding on the spacejunk
And it's bringing me to you
Riding on the space junk
Bringing me to you
Yeah!
It's bringing me to you
Girl, yeah
Oh!
It's bringing me to you
It's bringing me to you.